Begin to find those areas you need to surrender;
areas you need to confess in your life.
You know yourself more than anyone because what is about to happen
is destined for you to be free.
Yes, I am very sure you'll be released today.
You will begin to count your blessings after this prayer.
Tell your neighbor, "I will begin to count my blessings after this prayer".
Halleluyah!
Viewers all over the world, be ready to begin to count your blessings after the prayer.
Whatever medium you are using to view us, it is the will of God to bless you.
I say, it is the will of God to heal you.
It is his way to deliver you.
You know that?
[Yes.]
Okay, begin to show that faith, that belief.
So if you believe that, you begin to confess your blessing, your breakthrough.
Whilst you are waiting to receive, confess it.
Whilst I'm waiting to receive the blessing, I say, "Thank You Jesus, I am blessed".
That is the heart of faith.
Father, we thank You.
Holy Spirit, we thank You.
We thank You.
We recognize Your presence.
Yes, we are welcome.
Say, "I am welcome."
"I'm conscious that I'm welcome."
Say, "I'm welcome."
I say, "I am welcome."
Father, we thank You.
What can hinder you or stop you in the presence of God?
I can´t hear you.
[Nothing!]
Say to yourself, "What can stop me in the presence of God?
Because His presence is mighty.
What can stop my blessing? What can stop my healing in the presence of Jesus?"
Jesus!
I surrender!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Holy Spirit.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Spirit of Deliverance.
Holy Spirit, Spirit of deliverance.
Say, "Rain on me, Lord."
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Rain on me, Lord - Your Spirit of deliverance!
Wherever that evil spirit, that spirit that stops you, that spirit that gives you pain and affliction...
I say, "That spirit!"
Out!
"That spirit!"
Say, "That spirit!"
Command them out.
Come out!
Watch your screen.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Holy Spirit, rain on Your children!
Rain on us - Your Spirit of deliverance!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Watch your screen and see what is happening right now.
Demons are already manifesting in the lives of the people
and people who have eaten poison are vomiting them out.
In the mighty name of JesusI
Amen!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I command that affliction to leave you!
That spirit of limitation, I command them out!
I command them to leave you!
That disease in your blood to leave you!
That disease in your kidney to leave you!
Wherever that disease is located,
wherever it is located - that affliction -
right now, command them out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
That affliction!
Continue to watch your screen.
Vomiting Of Poisonous Substances
The poison they have eaten from the table of the enemy - they are vomiting it out right now.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Viewers out there, distance is not a barrier. Stay connected.
I command them out!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Now watch your screen.
You can see clots of blood in what that person is vomiting out.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Viewers, anywhere you are, distance is not a barrier.
Right now, you can begin to claim your blessing, your deliverance
as it is happening right here in the Arena of Liberty.
You can see the people still vomiting out all the poisonous substances in their system.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Command them out!
Continue to watch your screen. This is the time you have been waiting for.
Begin to use your faith to put a demand on this anointing.
You can see that man vomiting out all the poisonous substances in his system right now.
In the mighty name of Jesus!
You know something is going on but you don't know the level.
The Spirit of God is everywhere in your organs;
He is everywhere right now in your system, searching for the affliction.
Right now, will you allow Him to search?
Right now, command the affliction!
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Command the affliction!
Command that sickness, that disease!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
You see the power of God still flushing out the poisonous substance in his system.
This one has been given pain and agony for so many years.
It is what the Spirit of God is flushing out right now.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Continue to watch your screen.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Holy Ghost!
Command that affliction!
In the name of Jesus, command the affliction!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Bring them out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Disease, sickness and affliction in their system is what they are vomiting out.
Vomiting Blood And Poisonous Substances
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the name of Jesus!
Whatever hinders your blessings,
whatever hinders your healing,
give way, in the name of Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Be it doubt - give way, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever hinders your healing, whatever hinders your deliverance,
I command them to give way, in the name of Jesus!
I say, Give way!
Whatever you think might have hindered your healing, your deliverance,
I command them to give way!
Right now, connect to your healing! Connect to your deliverance!
Begin to connect to your healing, to your deliverance!
What they are pouring out from their system, it is not their will to pour this out
but the Spirit of God is flushing out the affliction, sickness and disease in their system right now.
In the name of Jesus!
You are decreed to be here today.
You are decreed to be delivered.
That is why I will not leave you until you are delivered.
If you take my word, let me hear you.
If you believe in my word, let me hear you.
[Amen!]
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah!
Watch your screen. See the clot of blood in what that person is vomiting out.
[Amen!]
Whatever that is hiding, wherever it is in your organ,
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Be free in the name of Jesus!
Yes, the Word of God will free you! He sent forth His Word and He delivered them.
[Amen!]
Yes, whatever, wherever that pain, that affliction, whatever name - cancer, deadly disease,
be captured in the name of Jesus!
That poison!
[Out!]
That fibroid!
That cancer!
[Out!]
Whatever situation, I command you to cease, in the name of Jesus!
Be ceased in the name of Jesus!
Yes, walk with me in the Spirit. You will see what is going on.
The cherubim - they are everywhere.
They are everywhere, locating those who are sick.
Wherever, whatever situation, whatever name,
wherever it is located, right now, operation is going on.
Open your lips and release yourself. Say, "Thank You, Lord!"
Someone is working in the person of the Holy Ghost.
Holy Ghost!
In my blood - Holy Ghost!
In my bones - Holy Ghost!
In my kidneys - Holy Ghost!
In my liver - Holy Ghost!
In my organs - Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Those who have pain in their breasts, whatever name they call it, cancer, lump - place your hand.
Wherever the position, wherever you have that pain - place your hand.
The healing hand of God wants to heal you.
The healing hand of God is on you.
Are you ready?
Place your hand wherever you have that pain.
If you have a loved one somewhere that is sick, stretch your hand.
Halleluyah!
Lay your healing hand, in the name of Jesus!
[Amen!]
Holy Ghost! Lay your healing hand, in the name of Jesus!
Lay your healing hand on me, in the name of Jesus!
Holy Ghost! Lay your healing hand on me, in the name of Jesus!
Holy Ghost!
In the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Let that pain be ceased!
That affliction be ceased!
In your blood, be ceased!
That affliction, be ceased!
In your kidney, be ceased!
In your liver, be ceased!
That affliction, be ceased!
In your womb, be ceased!
Wherever it is located, be ceased!
Say, "Be ceased!"
You affliction, be ceased!
Whatever you might have eaten on the table of your enemy!
[Out!]
Whatever you might have eaten in your dream!
Be flushed out, in the name of Jesus!
You just confess that affliction you have; confess that disease you have.
Yours is to confess and believe. Jesus is to heal.
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Somebody touched me
Somebody touched my soul
When I was praying
Praying to my Father
Somebody touched my soul
It must be Jesus
Jesus Christ touched my soul
When I was praying
Praying to my Father
Jesus Christ touched my soul
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
[Amen!]
I know you are released!
I say, I know you are released!
Right now, confess your release and give thanks to God.
Thank You, Lord, I am released.
Defeat and failure, sickness and affliction are things of the past.
Failure is a thing of the past.
Setback is a thing of the past.
I know I am released.
Sickness, disease are things of the past.
Defeat and failure are things of the past.
Setback is a thing of the past.
Limitations are things of the past.
I know I am released! Thank You, Jesus Christ!
Confess your release.
Viewers all over the world, be ready to begin to count your blessings after the prayer.
Whatever challenges you are facing, Jesus - with Him, all things are possible.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
For those on the sickbed, that is not where you belong.
Afflictions in your blood are things of the past, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Anywhere in your organs - be free, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear you being free, in the name of Jesus!
That affliction is a thing of the past, in the name of Jesus!
Healing hands of Jesus are on you, in the name of Jesus!
Holy Ghost!
Begin to feel the freedom right now!
Begin to feel the healing!
In your bones, blood, kidneys, liver - freedom!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Jesus says, "It is over!"
That sickness is over!
The affliction is over!
That disease is over!
That limitation is over!
That setback is over!
That failure is over!
Limitation is over!
Stagnation is over, in the name of Jesus!
I want to hear from you, "It is over!"
Mean it - it is over!
From your heart - it is over!
Say it from your heart - It is over!
In the name of Jesus!
It is over.
When Jesus says, "It is over"...
I said when Jesus says, "It is over"...
The word I'm saying is not mine.
The word you hear from me is not mine.
I'm just a vessel; I'm just being used.
When Jesus says, "It is over", it is over!
I say, when Jesus says, "It is over", it is over!
Do you want to hear, "It is over!" from Jesus?
It is over!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
I said that disease, affliction, pain - it is over!
That should be your language.
- When Jesus says, "It is over"
- It is over!
- When Jesus says, "You are healed"
- I am healed!
- When Jesus says, "You are delivered"
- I am delivered!
- When Jesus says, "You are blessed"
- I am blessed!
- When Jesus says, "You are saved"
- I am saved!
What else?
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
He sent forth His Word.
Take note: The Word of Jesus is not the Word of man.
- When Jesus says, "You are healed"
- I am healed!
- When Jesus says, "You are delivered"
- I am delivered!
- When Jesus says, "You are blessed"
- I am blessed!
- When Jesus says, "You are free"
- I am free!
- When Jesus says, "You are saved"
- I am saved!
What else?
Overflow congregation
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You will not leave here without your freedom.
Right now, it is possible that you may not believe yourself but believe Jesus.
Tell your neighbour, "It is possible you may not believe yourself
because you are still feeling some slight, strange pain.
Believe Jesus!
Jesus says, "It is over!"
Jesus says, "You are healed!"
Jesus says, "You are delivered!"
Jesus says, "You are blessed!"
Jesus says, "You are saved!"
Tell your neighbour, "Jesus is not a man that lies".
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah.
Begin to rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Ask your neighbour, "Why are you rejoicing?"
Because it is over!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Because you want me to tell you to rejoice before you rejoice.
I have a way of telling you.
I know you because you don't believe yourself but you believe Jesus.
You don't believe yourself but you believe Jesus.
If I'm right, let me see your hand.
Rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Amen!
Ask your neighbour, "Why are you rejoicing?"
Because it is over!
That is the message I hear.
I was hearing breakthrough.
I said, "Father, you mean breakthrough?"
He said, "It is over!"
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Amen!
I rejoice with you.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Viewers, the word 'breakthrough' from Father, Jesus means, it is over!
When Jesus says, "You are healed", you are healed.
When Jesus says, "You are saved", you are saved.
When Jesus says, "You are blessed", you are blessed.
Jesus is not a man that lies.
You are free, in the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Why are you rejoicing?
Because it is over!
Overflow Congregation
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Hallelujah! I want to rejoice with you once again.
Take this word as you are going now.
The word with you is: "It is over!"
- And who said, "It is over!"?
- Jesus!
- And when Jesus says, "It is over!"
- It is over!
So take it. Continue to meditate over this.
When you hear anything strange like the message we preached today -
that you don't need to look far to find Him, you do not lie.
You don't need to look far.
Ah, you see it.
You look here and see economic oppression.
Here political oppression.
Everywhere religios oppression. So everywhere.
How do we react to this matter?
It is not that oppression now, but the way you react to it; sometimes, our reaction can lead to sin.
Can lead to what?
Sin.
When you say, "Oh, why are you doing this?
You are committing sin again.
You believe you are doing the right thing whereas you are committing sin.
Because the way you react to an issue matters.
Not that issue but the manner you react to it matters.
Let us be known as people who are for good, not just against the bad.
So take that message home.
This is my message to you today.
I want to leave you by saying, "It is over!"
Overflow Congregation
Continue to meditate this: "It is over!"
That sickness, disease, affliction, setback, stagnation, limitation, failure, nightmares - it is over!
I can´t hear you!
[It is over!]
What the Lord has done for me
I cannot tell it all
He saved me
And washed me in His blood
So I can shout
Hallelujah
Praise the Lord
So I can shout
Hallelujah
Praise the Lord
What the Lord has done for me
I cannot tell it all
He saved me
And washed me in His blood
Hallelujah!
Face your neighbour now and begin to count your blessings.
Share your testimony.
Viewers all over the world, open your lips. Share your testimony to those who care to listen.
Hallelujah! What the Lord has done for you, you cannot tell it all.
Hallelujah!
In Jesus' name.
That is just the beginning.
What you have said will not come back to your mouth.
He shall do it; it shall happen!
Thank You, Lord.
Right now for your nation. Whatever you have as a symbol or contact, stretch it.
Ask the Lord, the Redeemer to intercede in the affairs of your nation.
He's the Redeemer.
Open your lips and commit your nation.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Commit your nation.
God's intervention!
In Jesus Christ's name.
Commit your leader, the economy of your nation, the political situation of your nation.
God's intervention!
In Jesus Christ's name.
For those of us who are coming for the first time:
You have seen that Jesus is the same yesterday, today and forever.
You have seen what you have read, what you have studied in the Bible.
You can see the presence of Jesus in His Word, Spirit and all other.
So right now, you want to give your life and those who are here today to rededicate themselves.
Say after me: Lord Jesus, come into my heart.
Wash me with Your precious blood
and make me Your channel,
Your channel of love,
Make me Your channel,
Your channel of pardon.
Your channel of forgiveness.
Make me Your channel,
Your channel of purity.
Make me Your channel, Lord,
Your channel of shining light.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
[Amen!]
I can´t hear you..
Remember, you asked for a channel of God. You are a channel of God.
A channel of love - as you are going, there is hate everywhere.
Injustice, hatred and you are a channel of God, a channel of love.
Love your neighbour as yourself.
Your neighbour can be those who do not share the same faith with you.
Your neighbour can be your enemies - love them all.
Channel of shining light.
Out there, there is darkness and you are a shining light.
Don´t forget your promise to God: You are a channel.
I pray you remain a channel of God where there is darkness.
Where there is injury, you remain a channel of pardon.
Where there is sin, you remain a channel of forgiveness.
Where there is hate, you remain a channel of love.
In Jesus Christ's name.
[Amen!]
I can´t hear you..
Halleluyah!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Don´t forget whom you are.
I said, don´t forget whom you are.
There is an area that you have to take home.
We are going to make mistakes because there is no one righteous, not even one.
When you do, you must think about what you did.
That is, to examine your life.
It's a good thing.
Reflect and ask yourself, "Is this the kind of person I want to be?
A liar? A thief? A killer?"
Whatever you might have done, ask and examine yourself.
That is the special gift given to you, we call it 'discretion'.
"Oh no, this is not right. This is right."
Don't forget that.
Tell your neighbour, "Examine yourself.
"Examine your life - it's a good thing".
I can´t hear you..
[Examine your life - it's a good thing.]
Before you pray, when you wake up in the morning,
before you offer prayer to God, because God is God of justice,
sit down and examine your life.
Where you missed the mark - when you are not right and when you are right.
So that you can say, "Ah, I'm sorry, this is what I have done. I promised and I failed".
After that, you can now say, "Jesus! My Lord Jesus!"
If you don't examine your life before you pray, you are not praying to God -
you are praying to yourself.
Tell your neighbour, "If you have not examined yourself before you pray,
you are praying of yourself; you are saying words, not praying prayers.
When you wake up in the morning, before you pray, sit on your bed and
examine yourself, "What have I done? What happened?
This man promised me; I promised this one and failed. Oh, Lord Jesus".
You say to yourself, "I'm sorry" before you begin to pray.
That will guide you what to pray for.
You need a guide to pray.
If you don't have a guide to pray and you just wake up - whom are you praying to?
So please, thank you very much.
TT: Jacqueline Margaret
RV: Mel Flowers 23/09/2018